export const Data = [
    {
        question: "Javascript is an _______ language?",
        options: ["Object-Oriented", "Object-Based", "Procedural", "None of the above"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What does CSS stand for?",
        options: ["Central Style Sheets", "Cascading Style Sheets", "Cascading Simple Sheets", "Cars SUVs Sailboats"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following tag is used to insert a line-break in HTML?",
        options: ["<br>", "<a>", "<pre>", "<b>"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How to create an unordered list (a list with the list items in bullets) in HTML?",
        options: ["<ul>", "<ol>", "<li>", "<i>"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which character is used to represent the closing of a tag in HTML?",
        options: [" > ", " ! ", " / ", " . "],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following tag is used to make the underlined text?",
        options: ["<i>", "<ul>", "<u>", "<pre>"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following tag is used to define options in a drop-down selection list?",
        options: ["<select>", "<list>", "<dropdown>", "<option>"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "HTML tags are enclosed in-",
        options: ["# and #", "{ and }", "! and ?", "< and >"],
        answer:4
    },
    {
        question: "The <hr> tag in HTML is used for -",
        options: ["new line", "horizontal ruler", "vertical ruler", "new paragraph"],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following HTML attribute is used to define inline styles?",
        options: ["style", "type", "class", "None of the above"],
        answer:1
    },
];